null
came to change.
We come from 2021 and 2020
Nice years where everything went up.
But in 2022 became one year
that no one could have predicted.
An inflation that went from 0 % to 10 %.
Interest rates that were at minus
as now at 2.5%
mortgage rates
up to 4 percent.
Russia's evil entry, the war in Ukraine.
This and much more.
Got devastating consequences for the stock exchange
is 20 22.
There were many incidents that occurred under 20 22 that
Very few could have predicted.
In this video I want to go through how my
Twenty -sided two have gone there.
I will go through my overview at Avanza.
I hope you may have given the fuck in the sales button exactly
As I usually advise,
Play SEK 89,000.
And Castellum minus eighty thousand kronor.
Juicy sums there so really
And now we'll see what the countries look like you have the most
Money invested in Sweden about ninety percent
a little u s a and then a little other in scattered then
and now we get into funds
What do we have on funds then yes we see the companies that are most
Owned in the funds
Investor that I invested a great deal in Industrivärden
Lundbergs Kinnevik and Hexagon
a little recovery in perhaps the last half of the year
Hope I at
maybe that inflation begins to come down a little neighbor and
That you do not have to raise interest rates so much.
It may probably give
A small spark for the stock exchange to recover, I think.
How did it go for you under twenty -twenty -two write?
Great this below and I really want to know
If you have any tips on more videos that you think I
will do wonders for the year, twenty -twenty
hopefully so the year will go better than it